http://www.chickworkholding.com/4dcgi/public/site/privacy.shtml

Okuma
View All »
E-Series
View All »
E-Series
View All »
E-Series
View All »
Support
Contact Us
Local Support
Register Your Products
View All »
Privacy Policy
The following policy outlines and discloses how ChickWorkholding.com gathers and uses your personal information that we've gathered online, in person, or through the mail. If you have any questions or concerns about this policy or our use of your personal information, please contact us.
ChickWorkholding.com Privacy Policy
Chick Workholding Solutions believes in protecting the privacy of its customers. The purpose of this privacy policy is to describe the kinds of information that we may gather about you; how we may use that information; how we protect it; when we may disclose it; and the choices you have regarding your information.
By visiting the site, you are consenting to the practices described in the current version of this privacy policy. If you have visited our site previously, please review the privacy policy again to be sure you are familiar with its present terms.
Non-Personal Information That We Collect
We automatically collect non-personally identifiable information from you when you visit our site. This information includes your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. This number does not identify your name, email address, or other personal information. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site.
We also collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of cookies. A cookie is an alphanumeric file that a website puts on your hard drive so that it can remember something about you while you are using the site or when you return to the site. Cookies make it easier for you to use our site.
We use cookies to gather certain usage information about the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and individual pages of our site. This data helps us improve the appearance and usability of the site. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information nor do we combine information collected through these cookies with other personally identifiable information about you.
Personal Information That We Collect
We may collect your personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address and phone number in the course of processing your request for a product quote or when you register your products, or when we otherwise communicate with you.
Uses of Your Information
Contact information from the request for quote or product registration forms is used to send you information that you've requested from us. At the time that you register this information on our site, you may also be given an option to receive future information and email messages from us.
If you register for email or if you provide your email address to us, we will send you emails. These emails will inform you of new product launches, special promotions or offers, upcoming events, relevant news stories about our company, or other topics that we believe would interest you. If you currently receive our emails and do not wish to continue receiving them, please see the How to Remove or Correct Your Personal Information section below.
Disclosures of Your Information
We never share your name or address, e-mail address or other personally identifiable information to other companies, persons or agencies, except for the purposes described below:
Service Providers: We employ other companies and individuals to perform certain services and functions on our behalf. Examples include operating and maintaining our site, processing requests for quotes, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information, analyzing data, providing marketing consultation and assistance, distributing customer surveys, and providing customer service. Such companies may have access to personal information needed to perform their services or functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
For Your Protection and Ours: We may release personally identifiable information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with applicable law regulation, legal process, or governmental request; enforce or apply our Terms & Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Chick Workholding Solutions, our customers, our employees or others.
How to Remove or Correct Your Personal Information
Should you decide not to receive future communications, or to no longer receive our service, or to not share your name and address with other companies, the options for removing or correcting your personal information are as follows:
You may use this online form to contact us. Choose "website" from the category menu at the top of the page and then leave a detailed message in the text box at the bottom of the form.
You may send mail to the following address:
Chick Workholding Solutions
500 Keystone Drive
Warrendale PA 15086
You may call the following telephone number: 724.772.1644.
External Links
If any part of the ChickWorkholding.com website links you to other websites, those sites do not operate under this privacy policy. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
ChickWorkholding.com may update this privacy policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this privacy policy by sending a notice to the email address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy or security of your information, you may contact us in any of the following ways:
You may use this online form to contact us. Choose "website" from the category menu at the top of the page and then leave a detailed message in the text box at the bottom of the form.
You may send mail to the following address:
Chick Workholding Solutions
500 Keystone Drive
Warrendale PA 15086
You may call the following telephone number: 724.772.1644.
© 2009 Chick Workholding Solutions. All rights reserved.
